

# **MUHAMMAD UKASHA**

## Wordpress Developer

+92 3083089235 - ukashamughal3.0@gmail.com House No 36, Rajput Colony TandoAllahyar Pakistan

### **ABOUT ME**

I'm Ukasha a Frontend Developer Expert with 4 years of experience I love creating websites using code and wordpress. I am your go-to-person for converting PSD and Figma files to attractive websites. From creating optimized websites to fixing bugs. I always try to make websites look great work and work efficiently. I'm all about creating stunning and attractive websites.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# The Coderz Hub https://thecoderzhub.com

March 2022 - June 2024

- · Expert in developing and customizing WordPress themes and plugins to meet client needs
- Utilized Elementor Page Builder to create stunning, responsive website designs
- · Converted PSD and Figma designs to fully functional WordPress websites

## Working as a part time Freelancer

August 2021 - Present

- Creating WordPress websites from scratch
- Developing and customizing themes and plugins to meet client needs
- · Utilizing Elementor Page Builder to create stunning, responsive website designs
- Managing website design, content, and basic SEO to enhance online presence
- Converting PSD and Figma designs into fully functional WordPress websites with precise attention to detail

### **EDUCATION**

## **INTERMEDIATE (Inter Pass)**

2022 - 2024

From KAIM KHAN MEMORIAL HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL

#### **SKILLS**

Frontend Development, Wordpress Development, Theme Customization, Theme Development, Website Optimization, Elementor Page Builder, Woocommerce

### **PROJECTS**

- https://w3master.co.uk/wp-working/
- https://wordpress-1295436-4707172.cloudwaysapps.com/
- https://billzstore.com/
- https://demo.aspiredesignbyshah.com/
- https://traveldreamsdiary.com/
- https://carlazbell.com/
- https://zentouchheaven.com/roofing/
- https://w3master.co.uk/staging2/